# **DANIEL POMAREDA**

# IT Recruiter / Web Developer Junior

## **RESUME**

8+ years working as a Recruiter, 3+ as an IT Recruiter and Degree from Digital House as a Web Developer, experience working in IT Recruiting Agency, Advertising, Transportation, Finance, Retail and Mining. I consider myself as a committed and creative person, with initiative to reduce over time and keep looking for better results.

Currently, Im Looking for Web Developer position where I can implement all my skills.

**Tech Skills:** SASS, Javascript, Node, React, Hooks, Npm, Vite, Java, Springboot, Lombok, Junit, Mysql, MongoDB, AWS, S3, EC2, Docker, Vagrant, bash, Github

# **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

Zoluxiones Perú | IT Consulting Agency | IT Recruiter | Jan.2023 until Today

Sourcer, Prescreening, do informs and Interview developers from ALL OVER THE WORLD, working for Internacional Client, looking IT Candidates like: Fullstack, Backend, Frontend, Database Engineer, QA Automation, Digital Tranformation Manager, DevOps, Architect, Salesforce, Pega Developer, Wordpress, Mobile Developer, Scrum, Teach Lead, Digital Marketing

Experis - Manpower | IT Consulting Agency | IT Talent Sourcer | Mar. 2022 – Dec. 2022

 Source, Prescreening, do informs and Interview developers from PERÚ and LATAM, such us: Fullstack, Backend, Frontend, Database Engineer, QA Automation, QA Functional, Digital Tranformation Manager, DevOps, Architect, Security, Technical LAN, Infrastructure, Cloud Enginner.

P'Cofit | IT Recruiting Agency | IT Talent Hunter | Oct. 2021 – Feb. 2022

 Source, Hunt, Pre-Screen and Interview Seniors LATAM-USA developers, such us: Fullstack, Backend, Frontend, Database Engineer, QA Automation, Project Manager, QA Lead, Technical Project Manager, DevOps, Product Designer, FullStack .Net Developer, Marketing Specialist.

CIRCUS GREY PERU | Advertising Agency | HR Analyst | Oct. 2019 – Mar. 2020

 In a charge of Recruitment processes. Evaluate and design strategies to update new job profiles. Interview and evaluate candidates helping by psychology test. Develop on boarding process for new employees. Notify applicants of results of selection process and prepare job offers.

**TRANS. H. A.** Transportation Company | HR Responsible | Mar. 2018 - Set. 2019

RECRUITER FREELANCER | Nov. 2016 until Today

**EKA MINING S.A.C.** | Mining Company | HR Assistant | Jun. 2015 - Oct. 2016

ELEKTRA – AZTECA BANK | Retail - Bank | HR intern | Apr. 2014 - Apr. 2015

# **CONTACT:**

**Location:** Urb. La Colonial, Callao, Lima, Perú

Mail: pomaredaniel@gmail.com

## Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/itrecruiter-daniel-henry-pomareda-castro

#### Github:

https://github.com/Daniel-Pomareda

# **EDUCATION:**

DEGREE – 2015:

Organizational Psychologist San Martín de Porres University

- HR DIPLOMA 2016 PUCP
- Advance English 2021:
  Idiom Pacific University
- IT Recruiting 2021:
  Recruiting Skull Level Nº1
- Certified Tech Developer
  April 2022 2023:
  Digital House

#### KNOWLEDGE:

- Recruiting IT, Sourcing, Linkedin Recruiter, Boolean code, Google X-ray
- Photoshop, Illustrator y Corel– Básico
- Digital Marketing